A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.2, Series 300 Latin America - Series 833 Lebanon FA387b
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Greece, 1951-1971; 749; 3 box(es)
  - Greece - Social Sciences, 749.S
    - Center of Economic Research, Athens - Publications, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Center of Economic Research, Athens - Publications, 1965-1967, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Center of Economic Research, Athens - Publications, 1965-1967, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Center of Economic Research, Athens - Publications, 1965-1967, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - State-Scholarships Foundation, Athens - Dimaras, Constantin Th., 1957 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Greece - Virus Studies, 749.V
    - University of Athens, 1959-1962 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Hungary, 1920-1966; 750; 3 box(es)
  Three subseries as follows: 750 (No program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area) 750 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings) 750 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture)
  - Banhalmi, George, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cserepfalvi, MIklos, 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Farkas, Emery, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Halasz, Imre, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Hungarian Red Cross - Medical Books, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Jonas, Paul, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Kassay, Dezso, 1956-1958, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Kemeny, Gabor, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lassovszky, Karoly, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lengyel, Peter, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Lissak, Kalman, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Mueller, Ivan, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Refugee Program, 1956 (November-December) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Refugee Program, 1956 (November-December) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Refugee Program, 1956 (December) - 1966 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Refugee Program, 1956 (December) - 1966 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Refugee Program, 1956 (December) - 1966 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Refugee Program, 1956 (December) - 1966 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Refugee Program, 1956 (December) - 1966 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Refugee Program, 1956 (December) - 1966 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Refugee Program, 1956 (December) - 1966 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Refugee Program - Evaluation, 1959-1963 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Refugee Program - Reports, 1956-1957, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Refugee Program - Reports, 1956-1957, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Tomasz, Alexander, 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Zathureczky, Ede, 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Hungary - Medical Sciences, 750.A
    - Emergency Aid, 1920-1926, 1932, 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Emergency Aid, 1920-1926, 1932, 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Emergency Aid, 1920-1926, 1932, 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Emergency Aid, 1920-1926, 1932, 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Hungary - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 750.D
    - Straub, F. Bruno, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Toth, Laszlo, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Italy, 1946-1969, 1977-1978; 751; 17 box(es)
  Nine subseries as follows: 751 (no program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area) 751 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings) 751 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture) 751 F Declinations (within program, or outside program but receiving more consideration than a flat declination, i.e. request circulated to a number of officers for opinion before declining; outside opinion solicited; considerable correspondence leading to the declination) 751 I Malaria 751 K Health services (epidemiology, reform, public health administration, laboratories, vital statistics, and particularly sanitary engineering) 751 R Humanities and arts 751 S Social sciences 751 V Virus studies
  - Casini, Guido, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Institute and Museum for the History of Science, 1961-1963, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Institute of Hygiene and Public Health - Housefly Study, 1952-1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Institute of Hygiene and Public Health - Visits, 1948-1952 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Institute of Technology, Milan - Cambi, Franco, 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Sardinia - Public Health, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - University of Milan - Giovanardi, Augusto, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - University of Parma - Animal Behavior, 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - University of Pavia - Housefly Study, 1955-1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - University of Pavia - Housefly Study, 1955-1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - University of Pavia - Housefly Study - Financial Material, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - University of Pavia - Housefly Study - Financial Material, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - University of Pavia - Housefly Study - Publications, 1954, 1956-1957, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Italy - Medical Sciences, 751.A
    - Furotes, Michelangelo G. F., 1960 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Institute of Experimental Psychology, Florence, 1947-1955 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - University of Bari - Clinical Medicine, 1952-1953, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - University of Bologna - Physiology - Equipment, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - University of Florence - Pharmacology, 1948-1952 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - University of Genoa - Anatomy, 1948-1951 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - University of Genoa - Neurophysiology, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - University of Genoa - Psychology, 1949-1951 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - University of Milan - Physiology, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - University of Naples - Baglioni, Corrado, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - University of Naples - Biochemistry - Fidanza, Flaminio, 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - University of Naples - Genetics - Anemia, 1951-1960 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - University of Naples - Genetics - Anemia, 1951-1960 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - University of Naples - Genetics - Anemia - Supplementary Material, 1949-1954, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - University of Naples - Genetics - Anemia - Supplementary Material, 1949-1954, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - University of Naples - Genetics - Montalenti, Giuseppe, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - University of Naples - Genetics - Siniscalco, Marcello, 1958, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - University of Naples - Genetics - Symposium, 1958-1960 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - University of Parma - Human Genetics, 1954-1965 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - University of Parma - Human Genetics, 1954-1965 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - University of Parma - Human Genetics, 1954-1965 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - University of Parma - Human Genetics, 1954-1965 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - University of Parma - Human Genetics - Reprints, 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - University of Pisa - Physiology, 1951-1965 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - University of Pisa - Physiology, 1951-1965 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - University of Pisa - Physiology, 1951-1965 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - University of Pisa - Physiology, 1951-1965 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - University of Pisa - Physiology, 1951-1965 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - University of Pisa - Physiology - Reports, 1951-1959 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - University of Pisa - Physiology - Reprints, 1950-1951, 1957-1958, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - University of Pisa - Physiology - Reprints, 1950-1951, 1957-1958, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - University of Sienna - Neurophysiology, 1956-1959 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - University of Turin - Genetics, 1958-1967 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - University of Turin - Genetics, 1958-1967 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - University of Turin - Neurological Clinic, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Italy - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 751.D
    - University of Turin - Corn Genetics, 1958-1964 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - University of Turin - Corn Genetics, 1958-1964 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - University of Turin - Corn Genetics - Reprints, 1961-1967 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Gorini, Luigi, 1953-1957 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Italian Institute of Hydrobiology, 1948-1949, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Lona, Fausto, 1948, 1952-1956 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Magni, Giovanni E., 1953, 1955-1957 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - University of Bari - Histology, 1955-1963 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - University of Bari - Plant Pathology, 1957-1959, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - University of Bari - X-Ray Crystallography, 1957-1960 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - University of Bologna - Anatomy, 1948-1956, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - University of Bologna - Anatomy, 1948-1956, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - University of Bologna - Anatomy, 1948-1956, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - University of Bologna - Proteins, 1953-1961 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - University of Bologna - Raunich, Lee, 1953-1955 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - University of Camerino - Enzyme Chemistry, 1956-1959 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - University of Camerino - Zoology, 1955-1960 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - University of Ferrara - Biochemistry, 1954-1958 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - University of Ferrara - Biochemistry, 1954-1958 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - University of Ferrara - Biochemistry, 1959-1960, 1962-1964 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - University of Florence- Plant Physiology, 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - University of Milan - Botany, 1948-1949, 1953-1955, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - University of Milan - Genetics, 1949-1950, 1952-1965 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - University of Milan - Leone, Vincenzo, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - University of Milan - Maccacaro, G. A., 1961 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - University of Milan - Marre. Erasmo, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - University of Milan - Zoology, 1947-1950, 1952-1956, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - University of Naples - Biochemistry, 1950-1953, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - University of Naples - Genetics, 1948-1962 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - University of Naples - Genetics, 1948-1962 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - University of Naples - Genetics, 1948-1962 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - University of Naples - Genetics - Reprints, 1958-1960 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - University of Naples - Microbiology, 1955-1956, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - University of Padua - Biochemistry, 1955-1962 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - University of Padua - Embryology, 1948-1956 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - University of Padua - Marcuzzi, Giorgio, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - University of Padua - Proteins, 1956-1963 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - University of Padua - Proteins, 1956-1963 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - University of Padua - Toniolo, Lucio, 1950, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - University of Padua - Virology, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - University of Palermo - Embryology, 1952-1962 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - University of Palermo - Embryology, 1952-1962 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - University of Palermo - Embryology, 1952-1962 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - University of Palermo - Embryology, 1952-1962 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - University of Palermo - Embryology, 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - University of Palermo - Embryology - Nakano, Eizo, 1955-1958 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - University of Palermo - Embryology - Reprints, 1954-1957, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - University of Palermo - Embryology - Reverberi, Guiseppe, 1953-1955, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - University of Palermo - Embryology - Reverberi, Guiseppe - Reprints, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - University of Palermo - Monroy, Alberto, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - University of Palermo - Plant Physiology, 1955-1961 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - University of Parma - Pharmacology, 1955-1963 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - University of Parma - Pharmacology, 1955-1963 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - University of Parma - Pharmacology - Reprints, 1954, 1957-1962 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - University of Parma - Pharmacology - Reprints, 1954, 1957-1962 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - University of Pavia - Biochemistry, 1950-1951, 1953-1956 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - University of Pavia - Ciferri, Raffaele, 1952-1953, 1955, 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - University of Pavia - Corn Genetics, 1956-1960 (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - University of Pavia - Corn Genetics, 1956-1960 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - University of Pavia - Frizzi, Guido, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - University of Pavia - Genetics, 1948-1963 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - University of Pavia - Genetics, 1948-1963 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - University of Pavia - Genetics, 1948-1963 (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - University of Pavia - Genetics - Annual Reports, 1957-1959 (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - University of Pavia - Spectroscopy, 1953-1958 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - University of Pisa - Animal Behavior, 1957-1962 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - University of Pisa - Genetics, 1953-1955 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - University of Rome - Biochemistry, 1948, 1950, 1953-1957 (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - University of Rome - Biochemistry, 1958-1964 (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - University of Rome - Biochemistry, 1958-1964 (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - University of Rome - Bone Structure, 1953, 1957-1962 (Box 10, Folder 119)
    - University of Rome - Embryology, 1948-1955 (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - University of Rome - Fasella, Paolo M., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - University of Rome - Genetics, 1960-1965 (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - University of Rome - Genetics, 1960-1965 (Box 10, Folder 123)
    - University of Rome - Nicoletti, Benedetto, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - University of Rome - Vaciago, Alessandro, 1963, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - University of Rome - X-Ray Crystallography, 1953, 1955-1965 (Box 10, Folder 126)
    - University of Sassari - Leone, Enzo, 1953, 1956, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 127)
    - University of Turin - Animal Behavior, 1953, 1957-1961 (Box 10, Folder 128)
    - University of Turin - Institute of Anatomy, 1949-1952 (Box 10, Folder 129)
    - Zoological Station of Naples - Dohrn, Peter, 1954-1955 (Box 11, Folder 130)
    - Zoological Station of Naples - Library, 1955-1959 (Box 11, Folder 131)
    - Zoological Station of Naples - Library - Publications, 1950-1958 (Box 11, Folder 132)
  - Italy - Declinations, 751.F
    - Sardinia - Socio-Economic Study, 1950-1952 (Box 11, Folder 133)
  - Italy - Malaria, 751.I
    - Insecticides, 1947-1954 (Box 11, Folder 134)
    - University of Pavia, 1948-1958 (Box 11, Folder 135)
    - University of Pavia, 1948-1958 (Box 11, Folder 136)
  - Italy - Health Services, 751.K
    - University of Naples, 1949-1950, 1953-1957 (Box 11, Folder 137)
    - University of Naples, 1949-1950, 1953-1957 (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - University of Naples, 1958-1961 (Box 12, Folder 139)
    - University of Naples - Reports, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 140)
    - University of Rome, 1946-1952 (Box 12, Folder 141)
  - Italy - Humanities and Arts, 751.R
    - Center of Methodological Studies - American Thought, 1954-1957 (Box 12, Folder 142)
    - Instituto Italiano - Tibetan Studies, 1959-1964 (Box 12, Folder 143)
    - Instituto Per L'Oriente - Near Eastern Studies, 1950-1958 (Box 12, Folder 144)
    - Instituto Statale D'Arte Per la Cerramica, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 145)
    - Italian Institute of Historical Studies, 1948-1953 (Box 12, Folder 146)
    - Italian Institute of Historical Studies, 1948-1953 (Box 12, Folder 147)
    - Italian Institute of Historical Studies, 1948-1953 (Box 12, Folder 148)
    - Italian Institute of Historical Studies, 1954-1961 (Box 13, Folder 149)
    - Italian Institute of Historical Studies, 1954-1961 (Box 13, Folder 150)
    - Italian Institute of Historical Studies, 1954-1961 (Box 13, Folder 151)
    - Italian Institute of Historical Studies - de Caprariis, Vittorio, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 152)
    - Scuola Normale Superiore, Pisa, 1949-1952 (Box 13, Folder 153)
    - Scuola Normale Superiore, Pisa, 1949-1952 (Box 13, Folder 154)
    - Scuola Normale Superiore, Pisa, 1949-1952 (Box 13, Folder 155)
    - Scuola Normale Superiore, Pisa - Calogero, Guido, 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 156)
    - Scuola Normale Superiore, Pisa - Philosophy, 1956-1958 (Box 13, Folder 157)
    - Scuola Normale Superiore, Pisa - Reports, 1947-1948 (Box 13, Folder 158)
    - University of Cagliari - American Studies, 1953-1955 (Box 13, Folder 159)
    - University of Milan - Cybernetics, 1951, 1954-1956, 1959-1960, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 160)
    - University of Milan - Rossi-Landi, Ferruccio, 1958-1961 (Box 14, Folder 161)
    - University of Padua - Film Center, 1948-1955 (Box 14, Folder 162)
    - University of Pisa - American Literature, 1953, 1956-1959 (Box 14, Folder 163)
    - University of Rome - American Studies, 1949-1954 (Box 14, Folder 164)
    - University of Rome - Philosophy Translations, 1952, 1954-1960 (Box 14, Folder 165)
    - Valle, Silvano, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 166)
    - Valle, Silvano, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 167)
  - Italy - Social Sciences, 751.S
    - ESMOI, 1952-1955, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 168)
    - Gasparini, Innocenzo, 1950-1954 (Box 14, Folder 169)
    - Giustiniani Archives, 1959-1961 (Box 14, Folder 170)
    - Istituto di Economia Internazionale, 1947-1951 (Box 14, Folder 171)
    - Istituto per Gli Studi di Economia, 1947-1953 (Box 15, Folder 172)
    - Italian Institute of Historical Studies - De Caprariis, Vittorio, 1959-1961, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 173)
    - Ivrea Community Study, 1953-1955 (Box 15, Folder 174)
    - Societa Italiana per la Organizzazione Internazionale - Anziolotti's Works, 1952-1956 (Box 15, Folder 175)
    - University of Catania - Cippola, Carlo, 1952-1954 (Box 15, Folder 176)
    - University of Florence - Conti, Ello, 1952-1954 (Box 15, Folder 177)
    - University of Florence - Political Science, 1956-1961, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 178)
    - University of Florence - Political Science - Reports, 1956-1958, 1961, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 179)
    - University of Genoa - Economics, 1953-1958 (Box 15, Folder 180)
    - University of Genoa - Economics, 1953-1958 (Box 15, Folder 181)
    - University of Genoa - Economics, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 182)
    - University of Genoa - Economics - Publications, 1954-1957 (Box 16, Folder 183)
    - University of Genoa - Economics - Publications, 1954-1957 (Box 16, Folder 184)
    - University of Genoa - Economics - Publications, 1954-1957 (Box 16, Folder 185)
    - University of Genoa - Fossati, Eraldo, 1953-1956 (Box 16, Folder 186)
    - University of Genoa - Scarpelli, Uberto, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 187)
    - University of Milan - Scarpelli, Uberto - Publications, 1949, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 188)
    - University of Milan - Vigezzi, Brunello, 1959, 1961-1965, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 189)
    - University of Milan - Vigezzi, Brunello - Reprints, 1960-1961, 1963, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 190)
    - University of Pavia - Borsa, Giorgio, 1956-1957, 1960-1966, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 191)
    - University of Pavia - Borsa, Giorgio - Reprints, 1957-1958, 1964-1966 (Box 17, Folder 192)
    - University of Rome - Economics, 1949-1953 (Box 17, Folder 193)
    - University of Rome - Ferrarotti, Franco, 1960, 1962-1965 (Box 17, Folder 194)
    - University of Siena - Statistics, 1956-1959 (Box 17, Folder 195)
    - University of Turin - Political Science, 1957-1967 (Box 17, Folder 196)
    - University of Turin - Political Science, 1957-1967 (Box 17, Folder 197)
    - University of Venice - Books, 1948-1951 (Box 17, Folder 198)
    - University of Venice - Economic History, 1956-1961, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 199)
  - Italy - Virus Studies, 751.V
    - University of Perugia, 1951-1953, 1955-1959 (Box 17, Folder 200)
- Liberia, 1959-1971; 759; 1 box(es)
  Three subseries as follows: 759 (no program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area) 759 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture) 759 S Social sciences
  - Cuttington College, 1960-1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cuttington College, 1960-1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cuttington College, 1960-1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Davidson, Ralph Kirby - Liberia Diary - DAV-1, October 27-29, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Liberia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 759.D
    - Cuttington College - Agriculture, 1959-1961, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - University of Liberia - Horticulture, 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - University of Liberia - Ma, Paul C., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Liberia - Social Sciences, 759.S
    - Cuttington College, 1962-1969, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Cuttington College, 1962-1969, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Norway, 1936-1972; 767; 6 box(es); 6 __Boxes
  Six subseries as follows: 767 (no program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area) 767 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings) 767 C Nursing (nursing education, public health nursing) 767 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture) 767 R Humanities and arts 767 S Social sciences
  - Health - Bjornsson, Jon, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Health - Engedal, Knut, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Health- Salaries, 1945-1948, 1950-1951, 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Health- Statistical Division, 1946-1947, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Norway - Medical Sciences, 767.A
    - Norwegian Radium Hospital - Pihl, Alexander Abraham, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - University of Bergen - Gjestland, Trygve, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - University of Oslo - Human Genetics, 1952-1955, 1958-1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - University of Oslo - Marthinsen, Arne, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - University of Oslo - Neuroanatomy - Brodal Alf, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - University of Oslo - Neuroanatomy - Jansen, Jan, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - University of Oslo - Neurophysiology, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - University of Oslo - Psychiatry, 1936-1937, 1939, 1945-1958 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - University of Oslo - Psychiatry, 1936-1937, 1939, 1945-1958 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - University of Oslo - Psychiatry, 1936-1937, 1939, 1945-1958 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - University of Oslo - Psychology, 1949-1951 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - University of Oslo - Radiology, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - University of Oslo - Respiratory Physiology, 1949-1957, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - University of Oslo - Respiratory Physiology, 1949-1957, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - University of Oslo - Rovig, Gunnar, 1949-1951, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Veterinary High School - Physiology, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Norway - Nursing, 767.C
    - Developmental Aid, 1945-1948, 1950-1951, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Norway - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 767.D
    - Braarud, Trygve, 1951-1952, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Norwegian Radium Hospital - Biochemistry, 1950-1956 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Norwegian Radium Hospital - Eldjarn, Lorentz, 1956-1958 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - University of Bergen - Marine Biology, 1958-1961, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - University of Oslo - Biochemistry, 1952-1956, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - University of Oslo - Experimental Biology, 1945-1951 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - University of Oslo - Lund, Einar Wang, 1951-1953 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - University of Oslo - Medical Biochemistry, 1956-1960 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - University of Oslo - Nordal, Arnold, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - University of Oslo - Nutrition, 1946, 1948-1951 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - University of Oslo - X-Ray Crystallography, 1950-1959, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 32)